{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, E, Q, P and directed edges Q->P, X->E, X->P, E->Q.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome P.", "answer": "[{'Q'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome P.", "answer": "{'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome P.", "answer": "{'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Q'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome P?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome P?\nA. set()\nB. {'X'}\nC. {'Q', 'X'}\nD. {'Q'}", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome Q?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "60232014", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes D, I, A, E and directed edges D->E, A->E, I->A, D->I.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment I and outcome E.", "answer": "[{'A'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment I and outcome E.", "answer": "{'A'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment I and outcome E.", "answer": "{'A'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'A'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment I and outcome E?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment I and outcome E?\nA. {'D'}\nB. set()\nC. {'A', 'D'}\nD. {'A'}", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment I and outcome E?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "39963389", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes U, S, I, K, Z and directed edges S->K, K->Z, U->S, I->Z.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment S and outcome Z.", "answer": "[{'K'}, {'K', 'I'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment S and outcome Z.", "answer": "{'K'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment S and outcome Z.", "answer": "{'K', 'I'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'K', 'I'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment S and outcome Z?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment S and outcome Z?\nA. {'U', 'I'}\nB. {'K', 'U'}\nC. {'K'}\nD. set()", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome Z?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "98590789", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, E, M, C, I and directed edges E->M, V->I, M->C, E->I, V->E, V->C.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome C.", "answer": "[{'M'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome C.", "answer": "{'M'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome C.", "answer": "{'M'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'M', 'I'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome C?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome C?\nA. {'V', 'I'}\nB. {'V', 'M'}\nC. set()\nD. {'M'}", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome C?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "93855978", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, U, L, N, C, X and directed edges U->N, E->X, N->C, L->C, E->N, E->U, U->L, L->X.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment U and outcome X.", "answer": "[{'L'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment U and outcome X.", "answer": "{'L'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment U and outcome X.", "answer": "{'L'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'L'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment U and outcome X?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment U and outcome X?\nA. {'C'}\nB. {'L'}\nC. {'N'}\nD. {'C', 'E'}", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment U and outcome X?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "67845896", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, V, R, E, F, P and directed edges H->R, R->E, E->F, R->P, V->P.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment R and outcome F.", "answer": "[{'E'}, {'V', 'E'}, {'P', 'E'}, {'V', 'P', 'E'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment R and outcome F.", "answer": "{'E'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment R and outcome F.", "answer": "{'V', 'P', 'E'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'V', 'E'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment R and outcome F?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment R and outcome F?\nA. {'H', 'E'}\nB. {'P', 'E'}\nC. {'H'}\nD. {'P', 'H'}", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment R and outcome E?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "70034848", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, T, A, B, P, R, I and directed edges T->I, P->R, F->P, T->B, F->T, P->I, T->A, A->I, B->P, A->P.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome P.", "answer": "[{'A', 'B'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome P.", "answer": "{'A', 'B'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome P.", "answer": "{'A', 'B'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'A', 'B'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome R?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome P?\nA. {'R', 'B', 'I'}\nB. {'A', 'B'}\nC. {'R', 'B', 'I', 'F'}\nD. {'A', 'R', 'B', 'I'}", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome P?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "19169990", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, J, K, W, M, X, I and directed edges O->I, O->M, J->W, M->I, J->K, W->X, J->I, J->M, W->I, K->X, O->J.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment J and outcome X.", "answer": "[{'K', 'W'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment J and outcome X.", "answer": "{'K', 'W'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment J and outcome X.", "answer": "{'K', 'W'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'K', 'W', 'X'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment J and outcome M?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment J and outcome X?\nA. {'O', 'W'}\nB. {'I'}\nC. {'K', 'W'}\nD. set()", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment J and outcome M?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "54340920", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Q, Y, O, B, N, J, K, T and directed edges O->B, O->K, B->N, Y->O, Q->J, Y->J, J->K, O->T.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment O and outcome N.", "answer": "[{'B'}, {'B', 'Q'}, {'T', 'B'}, {'T', 'B', 'Q'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment O and outcome N.", "answer": "{'B'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment O and outcome N.", "answer": "{'T', 'B', 'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'T', 'B', 'Q'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment O and outcome N?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment O and outcome N?\nA. {'J', 'B'}\nB. {'J', 'B', 'Y'}\nC. {'T', 'B', 'Y'}\nD. {'T', 'B', 'Q'}", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment B and outcome N?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "99838002", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, T, N, H, X, J, S, I and directed edges T->X, T->J, H->I, N->J, S->I, R->T, T->H, R->N, H->J.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome I.", "answer": "[{'H'}, {'H', 'S'}, {'H', 'X'}, {'H', 'S', 'X'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome I.", "answer": "{'H'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome I.", "answer": "{'H', 'S', 'X'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'H', 'S', 'X'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome I?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome I?\nA. {'R', 'X'}\nB. {'J', 'N', 'R'}\nC. {'H', 'X'}\nD. {'J', 'N', 'S'}", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome I?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "33074606", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, F, U, N, Y, G, X, A, R and directed edges B->R, N->X, U->Y, F->R, X->A, B->F, B->U, B->G, U->N.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment U and outcome X.", "answer": "[{'N'}, {'N', 'Y'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment U and outcome X.", "answer": "{'N'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment U and outcome X.", "answer": "{'N', 'Y'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'N', 'G', 'Y'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment X and outcome A?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment N and outcome A?\nA. {'B', 'Y', 'R', 'U', 'F', 'X'}\nB. {'X', 'B', 'U', 'Y'}\nC. {'X'}\nD. {'B', 'Y', 'U', 'F', 'X'}", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment N and outcome X?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "39622390", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, U, H, G, I, K, J, N, W and directed edges P->W, J->N, P->N, H->J, I->J, J->W, U->G, N->W, I->K, U->W, P->H.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome N.", "answer": "[{'J'}, {'J', 'U'}, {'J', 'I'}, {'J', 'G'}, {'J', 'U', 'I'}, {'J', 'U', 'G'}, {'J', 'I', 'G'}, {'J', 'U', 'I', 'G'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome N.", "answer": "{'J'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome N.", "answer": "{'J', 'U', 'I', 'G'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'J', 'G'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome N?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome N?\nA. {'J'}\nB. {'W', 'U', 'I', 'P', 'G'}\nC. {'W', 'U', 'I', 'P', 'J'}\nD. {'J', 'U', 'W'}", "answer": "A"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome W?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "30930220", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Y, A, K, W, directed edges K->W, Y->A, A->K and bi-directed edges Y<->W.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome W.", "answer": "[{'K'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome W.", "answer": "{'K'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome W.", "answer": "{'K'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'A', 'Y'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome W?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome W?\nA. {'Y'}\nB. {'K'}\nC. set()\nD. {'K', 'Y'}", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome W?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "19817392", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, Q, Z, R, directed edges T->Q, Z->R, Q->Z, T->R and bi-directed edges Q<->R.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment Q and outcome R.", "answer": "[{'Z'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment Q and outcome R.", "answer": "{'Z'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment Q and outcome R.", "answer": "{'Z'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'T'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment Q and outcome R?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment Q and outcome R?\nA. {'T', 'Z'}\nB. set()\nC. {'T'}\nD. {'Z'}", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment Z and outcome R?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "74324194", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes S, A, G, R, M, directed edges A->G, S->R, G->R, S->A, G->M and bi-directed edges A<->M, R<->M.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome R.", "answer": "[{'G'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome R.", "answer": "{'G'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome R.", "answer": "{'G'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'M'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome G?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome R?\nA. {'S'}\nB. {'G'}\nC. {'M'}\nD. {'M', 'S', 'G'}", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment G and outcome M?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "63443565", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, M, D, Q, W, directed edges K->M, Q->W, M->Q, D->W and bi-directed edges M<->D.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment M and outcome W.", "answer": "[{'Q'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment M and outcome W.", "answer": "{'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment M and outcome W.", "answer": "{'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Q'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment M and outcome W?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment M and outcome W?\nA. {'Q', 'D'}\nB. {'Q'}\nC. {'K', 'Q', 'D'}\nD. {'K', 'Q'}", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment M and outcome Q?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "28347361", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes O, B, Q, N, C, G, directed edges B->Q, O->Q, N->C, O->C, B->N, Q->G, O->B, O->G, B->G and bi-directed edges O<->C, O<->Q, B<->G, O<->G, N<->G, B<->Q.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment B and outcome C.", "answer": "[{'N'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment B and outcome C.", "answer": "{'N'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment B and outcome C.", "answer": "{'N'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'Q'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment B and outcome N?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment B and outcome C?\nA. {'N', 'Q'}\nB. {'Q', 'O', 'G'}\nC. {'N'}\nD. {'Q'}", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment N and outcome C?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "74839970", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, Y, A, D, T, B, directed edges P->A, Y->B, P->Y, T->B, A->D, A->T and bi-directed edges Y<->D.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome B.", "answer": "[{'T'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome B.", "answer": "{'T'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome B.", "answer": "{'T'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'T', 'Y'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome D?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome B?\nA. {'T'}\nB. {'T', 'D', 'Y'}\nC. set()\nD. {'D', 'Y'}", "answer": "A"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome B?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "55831986", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, E, A, H, S, O, W, directed edges E->W, A->W, E->S, B->E, H->O, O->W, H->S, B->H, A->H and bi-directed edges S<->W, B<->A, S<->O, E<->W.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome W.", "answer": "[{'O'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome W.", "answer": "{'O'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome W.", "answer": "{'O'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'O'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome W?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment H and outcome W?\nA. {'A', 'B', 'S', 'E'}\nB. {'A', 'B', 'O'}\nC. {'O'}\nD. {'E'}", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment E and outcome S?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "63543617", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes J, K, M, P, Q, O, X, directed edges P->X, Q->O, M->X, J->O, K->P, P->O, K->X, M->Q, J->K, O->X and bi-directed edges M<->Q, O<->X, J<->M.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome O.", "answer": "[{'P'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome O.", "answer": "{'P'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome O.", "answer": "{'P'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'P'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome O?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome O?\nA. {'P', 'M', 'X'}\nB. {'J', 'M', 'X'}\nC. {'P'}\nD. {'P', 'J', 'M', 'Q'}", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome O?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "55545932", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes G, L, I, C, S, W, N, K, directed edges G->N, G->L, C->N, L->C, G->I, G->C, N->K, L->K, I->N, C->K, L->S, S->W and bi-directed edges S<->K, G<->W, G<->N, I<->C, I<->W, C<->W, N<->K.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment L and outcome W.", "answer": "[{'S'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment L and outcome W.", "answer": "{'S'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment L and outcome W.", "answer": "{'S'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'K', 'C', 'S', 'G'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment I and outcome N?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment L and outcome W?\nA. {'N', 'S', 'C', 'I', 'G'}\nB. {'K', 'N', 'S', 'I', 'G'}\nC. {'S'}\nD. {'K', 'N', 'S', 'C', 'I', 'G'}", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment L and outcome N?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "03460334", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes F, Q, T, V, B, G, S, I, directed edges F->S, Q->I, G->I, V->G, V->I, F->I, V->S, T->V, V->B, Q->T, G->S and bi-directed edges T<->B.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome B.", "answer": "[{'V'}, {'V', 'F'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome B.", "answer": "{'V'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome B.", "answer": "{'V', 'F'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'B', 'Q'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome I?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome S?\nA. {'V', 'F'}\nB. {'F', 'B', 'I', 'Q'}\nC. {'V', 'B', 'I', 'G'}\nD. {'V', 'B', 'G'}", "answer": "A"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment T and outcome I?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "50153236", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes O, C, K, V, L, X, F, A, B, directed edges O->C, K->B, A->B, O->X, C->B, V->A, V->X, C->K, C->F, K->L, L->F, F->B and bi-directed edges O<->A, O<->C, V<->B, L<->B.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome F.", "answer": "[{'L'}, {'V', 'L'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome F.", "answer": "{'L'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment K and outcome F.", "answer": "{'V', 'L'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'V', 'K'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment C and outcome F?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment C and outcome L?\nA. {'X'}\nB. {'V', 'K'}\nC. {'K', 'X'}\nD. {'K', 'A', 'X'}", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment A and outcome B?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "72090191", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes I, Q, D, C, X, N, O, E, P, directed edges Q->X, D->X, D->C, C->E, Q->D, Q->P, N->E, O->P, D->O, C->X, I->Q, D->N and bi-directed edges D<->P, Q<->P, D<->O, Q<->O, N<->P, O<->P.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment D and outcome E.", "answer": "[{'N', 'C'}]"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one minimal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment D and outcome E.", "answer": "{'N', 'C'}"}, {"question_type": "FO", "question": "Find one maximal valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment D and outcome E.", "answer": "{'N', 'C'}"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is {'P', 'Q', 'O', 'X'} a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment D and outcome E?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following sets is a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment Q and outcome N?\nA. {'P', 'O', 'D'}\nB. {'D'}\nC. {'P', 'I', 'O'}\nD. {'D', 'C', 'I', 'P', 'E', 'X'}", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does there exist a valid frontdoor adjustment set for treatment Q and outcome E?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "12565170", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
